Leach, W. Barton (Walter Barton), 1900 -1971. Papers, 1920-1971: Finding Aid.
Papers, 1920-1971.
- CONTINGENT I
  - WRITINGS AND RESEARCH
    - "Perpetuities: Cy Pres on the March", Vanderbilt Law Review, October 1964, 33-18
      File contains correspondence; no copy of the article. Article was also published in Perspectives of Law: Essays for Austin Wakeman Scott;; Little, Brown Company, 1964; file does contain a copy of the article as published then (copy is dated January 18, 1963 and is a carbon of manuscript sent to Dean Roscoe Pound).
    - Book review by WBL of Bardot, M.P.? by A.P. Herbert, Harvard Law Review, December 1964, 33-19
      File contains correspondence and a copy of the article.
    - "Perpetuities: What Legislatures, Courts and Practitioners Can Do About the Follies of the Rule", The University of Kansas Law Review, 1965, No. 1., 33-20
      File contains correspondence and a copy of WBL's article.
    - "Perpetuities: The Nutshell Revisited", Harvard Law Review, March 1965, 33-21
    - Property Law Indicted or The People Vs. Blackstone, Kent, Gray and Stare Decisis (Accessories: Pontius Pilate and the Laws of the Medes and the Persians), University of Kansas Law School, March, 1966 4 folders, 33-22 to 34-2
      In March 1966, WBL gave a series of lectures with the above title at the University of Kansas Law School. The lectures were then published as a book by the University of Kansas Press in 1967.
      33-22 and 33-23 contain correspondence and several drafts of the lectures.
      34-1 and 34-2 contain correspondence relating to the publication of the lectures and a carbon copy of the manuscript. There are also copies of several reviews of the book.
    - "Divorce By Plane-Ticket in the Affluent Society, With a Side Order of Jurisprudence", University of Kansas Law Review, May 1966 3 folders, 34-3 to 34-5
      34-3 contains correspondence with The Yale Law Journal about the possibility of its publishing WBL's article.
      34-4 and 34-5 contain correspondence, two bills of particulars on the case at issue, several drafts of the article and a reprint of the article.
    - Shell Oil Company and Stafac. Inc., v. Henry Ouellette Sons Co., Inc. and Socony, Mobile Oil Co., Inc. 1967, 34-6
      WBL served as Amicus Curiae in this case, and a mimeographed copy of his Memorandum is enclosed.
    - "'Suicidal Admissions and Grading Policies of Our Law Schools', by Professor X of Y Law School", The Practical Lawyer, January 1967, 34-7
      File contains correspondence, drafts of WBL's article, and reprints from the New York Law Journal, March 1, 1967 and the New Jersey State Bar Journal for May 1967.
    - "Revisionism in the House of Lords: The Bastion of Rigid Stare Decisis Falls", Harvard Law Review, February 1967 2 folders, 34-8 to 34-9
      File contains notes, background materials (such as pamphlets on prospective overruling), correspondence and several drafts of WBL's article; also a reprint of the article in the New York Law Review, April 21, 1967.
    - "Associate Dean Casner Honored Or Would You Rather Have Berkeley?", Harvard Law School Bulletin, May 1967, 34-10
      Article relates to party given for Professor Casner on May 1, 1967.
    - "The Law at Harvard: A Quasi-Review With Personalia", Harvard Law School Bulletin, March 1968, 34-11
      File contains notes, correspondence and a copy of WBL's article which deals with Professor Arthur Sutherland's book The Law at Harvard.
    - Talks on American Law, revised edition, 1971, 34-12
      File relates to revision of book edited by Harold J. Berman, consisting to the texts of a series of broadcasts to foreign audiences by members of the Harvard Law School faculty, among them WBL. File contains correspondence but no copy of the text of WBL's broadcast.
    - Miscellaneous Writings and Speeches 2 folders, 35-1 to 35-2
    - Perpetuities Reform-General, 35-3
      File contains correspondence and background material (notes, reprints of articles, etc.); also a short letter from Mr. Justice Frankfurter.
    - Perpetuities Reform-Arizona, 35-4
    - Perpetuities Reform- Australia, 35-5
    - Perpetuities Reform-California, 35-6
    - Perpetuities Reform- Canada, 35-7
      File contains correspondence and a copy of the Ontario Law Reform Commission's Report on the Perpetuities Act, 1965.
    - Perpetuities Reform-Colorado, 35-8
    - Perpetuities Reform-Connecticut, 35-9
    - Perpetuities Reform-England, 35-10
    - Perpetuities Reform-Hawaii, 35-11
    - Perpetuities Reform-Idaho, 35-12
    - Perpetuities Reform-Ireland, 35-13
    - Perpetuities Reform-Kentucky, 35-14
    - Perpetuities Reform-Massachusetts 4 folders, 35-15 to 35-18
      35-15 and 35-16 contain correspondence.
      35-17 and 35-18 contain notes, various drafts of the bill which was eventually enacted and other background material. 35-18 contains two phonograph records prepared for the Harvard Law School Record telling the story of the bill (S. 361).
    - Perpetuities Reform-Missouri, 35-19
    - Perpetuities Reform-New Hampshire, 35-20
      File contains a carbon of a "Comment" written by WBL for the Harvard Law Review, December 1963 on the decision of the Supreme Court of New Hampshire In Re Sheldon Bassett Estate.
    - Perpetuities Reform- New Zealand, 35-21
      File contains much correspondence with David E. Allan (then Professor of Law,; Victoria University of Wellington) and a reprint of an article by Allan, "The Rule Against Perpetuities Re-Stated."
    - Perpetuities Reform-North Carolina, 35-22
    - Perpetuities Reform-Ohio, 36-1
    - Perpetuities Reform-Rhode Island, 36-2
    - Perpetuities Reform-Vermont, 36-3
    - Perpetuities Reform-Washington, 36-4
    - Perpetuities Reform-Wisconsin, 36-5
    - Ayer v. Philadelphia and Boston Face Brick Company, 36-6
      File contains correspondence and notes on the case and on its use by Mr. Stan Johanson for his L.L.M. thesis.
    - Carter v. Berry, 36-7
      File contains correspondence and notes re the decision in the case by the Mississippi Supreme Court. There is a reprint of the opinion in the case and of the opinion in the case of the Estate of Sarah G. Foster; also proof sheets for Part 24 of the American Law of Property, "The Common Law Rule Against Perpetuities", by WBL and Owen Tudor (for more on ALP, see WRITINGS AND RESEARCH: Leach and Tudor, The Rule Against Perpetuities).
      For more on Carter v. Berry and the issues involved, see WRTTINGS AND RESEARCH: "Perpetuities: Cy Pres on the March", Vanderbilt Law Review, October 1964.
    - Faus v. Pacific Electric Railway Company 2 folders, 36-8 to 36-9
      File contains correspondence; also briefs and opinions written at various stages of the development of the case.
    - Lucas v. Hamm, 36-10
      File contains correspondence; also briefs written at various stages of the development of the case.
    - Pierson v. Post, 36-11
      File contains correspondence with, among others, a descendant of both the families involved in the litigation.
    - Regina v. Ojibway, 36-12
      File relates to amusing case reported first in the Criminal Law Quarterly (Toron to 1965). WBL determined the authors of the prank and propagated it. File contains correspondence and a copy of the opinion in the case.
    - Salisbury v. Pearlman 3 folders, 36-13 to 36-15
      File relates to WBL's retention in the case by the Los Angeles firm of Greenberg and Glusker, attorneys for the defendants.
      36-13 contains correspondence; 36-14 and 36-15 contain briefs, notes and background material.
    - Wilson v. Johnson, 36-16
      File contains correspondence and both the Opinion of the Court of Appeals of Kentucky and a Dissent from that Opinion.
    - Zimmerman v. Shreeve, 36-17
      File contains memos on the case from WBL's students.
    - Miscellaneous Cases, 36-18
  - DEFENSE STUDIES
    The major portion of the material in this Series concerns matters relating to the Defense Policy Seminar which WBL helped establish at Harvard in 1954. Other groups of material deal with WBL's involvement in national defense matters beginning in the early 1950's, and with articles and speeches of WBL advocating a strong defense force.
    The material has been left in its original arrangement. Dates covered are 1951 to 1966.
    - Articles and Publications 11 folders, 37-1 to 37-11
      - (WBL) " Pentagon Prep School", Air Force Magazine, August 1955, 37-1
      - "A Presumptuous Course-Harvard's Defense Policy Seminar", Christian Science Monitor, August 1955, 37-2
      - (WBL) " Nine Reasons Why Our Airpower is Lagging", Air Force Magazine, September 1955, 37-3
      - (WBL) " British Views on Higher Defense Organization", Defense Policy Seminar Serial No. 83, Sept. 24, 1956, 37-4
      - (WBL) " American Problems of Forces and Organization", DPS Serial No. 87, October 11, 1956, 37-5
      - (WBL) " To the Next Secretary of Defense, A Respectful Memorandum", Air Force Magazine, Jan. 1957, 37-6
      - (WBL) Review of The Central Blue by Sir John Slessor, Air Force Magazine, February 1957, 37-7
      - (WBL) " National Need Vs. Personal Wish", Air Force Magazine, September 1957, 37-8
      - (WBL) " American Deficiencies in Military Research", The Listener, October 1957, 37-9
      - (WBL) DPS Serial No. 133, December 8, 1958, 37-10
      - (WBL) " Hobgoblins for the Gullible", Air Force Magazine, October 1960, 37-11
    - Lectures 24 folders, 37-12 to 37-35
      - The Boston Herald: Editorials, 37-12
      - The Boston Herald: Letters to the Editor, 37-13
      - The London Times: Articles, 37-14
      - (WBL) " A-B-C of the Air Force Build-up", The Boston Herald, December 18, 1951, 37-15
      - (WBL) " Filling the Gap", Time Magazine, March 21, 1955, 37-16
      - Congressional Investigation of Military Establishment, 37-17
      - "Academic Links for the Defense Department", Harvard Crimson, March 9, 1956, 37-18
      - Special Senate Subcommittee on Disarmament: Statement of WBL, March 9, 1956, 37-19
      - " Impact of Military Policy on Foreign Policy", Foreign Policy Course Lecture, University of Pennsylvania, July 12, 1956, 37-20
      - Lecture to Senior ROTC Officers, December 1956, 37-21
      - (WBL) " The Job of a Service Secretary", DPS Serial No. 103, December 27, 1956, 37-22
      - (WBL) " The Job of an American Service Secretary", Revue Militaire Generale, Paris, 37-23
      - (WBL) " American Problems of Forces and Organization", Royal United Services Institute (RUSI) Journal, February 1957, 37-24
      - "Are American Forces Adequate to Support Strategy?", Imperial Defence College Lecture (England), July 9, 11, 1957, 37-25 to 37-27
      - "Economics of National Defense", AFA Symposium, August 2, 1957, 37-28
      - Air Power Lectures, Ohio State University (Military history course), August 26, 27, 1957, 37-29
      - "Are American Forces Adequate to Support Strategy?" International Development Society Lecture, October 24, 1957, 37-30
      - "Pentagon Reorganization: 1958 Phase", Empire Trust Company, 37-31
      - "Forces and Strategy of the United States", Institute of World Affairs, Inc. Lecture, July 19, 1958, 37-32
      - Montgomery Memoirs (A Short Casebook on Ingredients of Decision in Military Affairs), DPS Serial No. 130, 37-33
      - Vietnam Panel Discussion, May 21, 1966, 37-34
      - Picture of WBL and Montgomery, Harvard Law School Bulletin, November 1955, 37-35
    - Materials-Lectures and Articles 36 folders, 38-1 to 39-22
      - Budget Session for Seminar, 38-1
      - History 138b, 1956-1957; Lectures on Airpower; Outline, 38-2
      - History 138b, Lecture No. 1, 38-3
      - History 138b, Lecture No. 2, 38-4
      - History 138b, Lecture No. 3, 38-5
      - Air Transport-Various Materials, 38-6
      - Operational Research-French Navy (Jean-Claude Peterschmitt), 38-7
      - British Senior Civil Service-Various Materials, 38-8 to 38-9
      - British Senior Civil Service Article, " The Dilemma of Discontinuity", by WBL, December 1956, 38-10
      - Economics of the Cold War, 38-11
      - Cordiner Report, 38-12 to 38-14
      - Disarmament-(Material) WBL Testimony on Disarmament, April 10, 1956, 39-1
      - Economics of National Defense, 39-2
      - Efficiency Report, Army Finance School, Aug. 15, 1813, 39-3
      - Gaither Report, 1958, 39-4
      - David H. Neiditz, Problems of German Rearmament, 39-5
      - " The Seminar in Defense Policy and Administration", Harvard Law School Bulletin, October 1955, 39-6
      - Manpower, 39-7
      - On Intelligent Reading of Defense Items in the Daily Press, 39-8
      - Public Information, 39-9
      - "The Military Lessons of Suez" by ELK, The Reporter, November 29, 1956, 39-10
      - News Items, 39-11
      - Research and Development (Reading Assignment No. 65), 39-12
      - Soviet Campaign, Analysis of, Re: Baldwin Article, April 27, 1956, 39-13
      - Spanish Bases, 39-14
      - Miscellaneous Speeches by WBL Re: Defense Policy and Military, 39-15
      - Korean Was Session-DPS 1956-1957 -October 17 and 24, 39-16 to 39-17
      - Navy-Material, 39-18
      - "Sputnik"- Harvard Law School Coffee Hour-Talk by WBL, October 15, 1957, 39-19
      - Sword and Swastika (Review), David H. Neiditz, 39-20
      - Twelve Myths About Air Power, Comment by WBL, July 1956, 39-21
      - "War Plans, Exercises and Maneuvers With Reference to the Budget", WBL, December 1956, 39-22
    - Defense Policy Seminar Distributions 7 folders, 39-23 to 39-29
      - Laredo Air Force Base, Texas, February 4, 1957, 39-23
      - Field Marshal Montgomery Session of DPS-Introductory Speech by WBL, November 15, 1955, 39-24
      - Gardner Forum (HLS): " Decision-Making", May 11, 1956, 39-25
      - "Building Leadership for National Defense," Mass. Workmen's Compensation Bureau -40th Anniversary Dinner, November 16, 1955, 39-26
      - Memorial Day Address, Weston, Mass., May 30, 1957, 39-27
      - Navy-OGC-Speech- April 14, 1957, 39-28
      - Harvard ROTC Units Speech, September 21, 1956, 39-29
    - Symposiums 4 folders, 40-1 to 40-4
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization Symposium, Harvard Defense Studies Program, March 23, 1957, 40-1
      - NATO Symposium, HDSP, March 23, 1957 -WBL Correspondence, 40-2
      - NATO Symposium, HDSP, March 23, 1957 -W.W. Wisely Correspondence, 40-3
      - NATO Symposium, HDSP, March 23, 1957 -Printed matter, programs, etc., 40-4
    - TV and Radio Programs 11 folders, 40-5 to 40-15
      - Backgrounds (Lyons); Various Scripts; Defense Studies Program, 40-5
      - Backgrounds; WGBH-TV, January 21, 1958; WBL, " The Case of General Gavin", 40-6
      - British Broadcasting Corporation Third Program, WBL Scripts, " American Politics and the United States Air Force", December 1956 and January 1957, 40-7
      - BBC: Feature Program on Ballistic Missiles for Re-broadcast, July 19, 1958, 40-8
      - BBC: " The Soviet Earth Satellite", Recorded October 21, 1957 for Broadcast in England October 22, 1957, 40-9
      - Backgrounds, October 17, 1957: "Montgomery's RUSI Lecture of October 12, 1955" -Lyons and WBL, 40-10
      - Radio-Backgrounds: " Government's Defense Policy", January 12, 1955 -Louis Lyons and WBL, 40-11
      - Radio: " On the Record", Harvard Station WHRB, December 9, 1957; Defense Matters, 40-12
      - Ford Foundation Report 1955-1956 -WBL, 40-13
      - Ford Foundation Report 1956-1957 -ELK, 40-14
      - Ford Foundation Report 1957-1958 -ELK, 40-15
    - Correspondence-A 3 folders, 40-16 to 40-18
      - Air Force- Historical Foundation, 40-16
      - Air Ministry, London, England, 40-17
      - Miscellany, 40-18
    - Correspondence-B 2 folders, 40-19 to 40-20
      - Booth, John-File contains a tape recording., 40-19
      - Miscellany, 40-20
    - Correspondence-C 4 folders, 41-1 to 41-4
      - Canadian Defence Material-Used by Peter Cumming for his paper in 1965., 41-1 to 41-3
      - Miscellany, 41-4
    - Correspondence-D 17 folders, 41-5 to 42-12
      - Defense Studies Program, 1953-1954, 1954-1955, 41-5
      - Defense Studies Program: Students, 1958-1959, 1959-1960; file contains much material re Mr. Philip Chapman and Mr. John E. Lawyer, Jr., 41-6
      - Defense Studies Program, 1961-1962, 1962-1963; file contains paper by Albert W.L. Moore, Jr., 41-7
      - Defense Studies Program, 1963-1964; file contains copies of research papers by Mr. John Stuart Higgins, Jr. and Mr. Woodrow B. Sneed., 41-8 to 41-9
      - Defense Studies Program, 1964-1965, 42-1
      - Defense Studies Program, 1966-1967, 42-2
      - Defense Studies Program, 1967-1968, 42-3
      - Defense Studies Program, 1968-1969, 42-4
      - Defense Policy Studies- University of California, Los Angeles, 1962, 42-5
      - Defense Studies Program (possibility)- University of Colorado; (Professor Jim Allen), 1962, 42-6
      - Defense Studies-Minnesota, 42-7
      - Defense Policy Seminar, Material on Untranscribed Disks, 42-8
      - Defense Studies Program-List of WBL's personal books in library., 42-9
      - Defense Studies Program-Publicity and News Items, 42-10
      - Department of Defense: Moyer, Burton B., Jr., 42-11
      - Defense Studies Program-Magazine Publications, 1955-1958; file contains bound volume., 42-12
    - Correspondence-E, 42-13
    - Correspondence-F, 42-14
    - Correspondence-G, 42-15
    - Correspondence-H 2 folders, 42-16 to 42-17
      - Huntington, Samuel P. (Professor), 42-16
      - Miscellany, 42-17
    - Correspondence-I 3 folders, 43-1 to 43-3
      - The Institute for Strategic Studies, London, England: Hon. A. Buchan, 43-1 to 43-2
      - Miscellany, 43-3
    - Correspondence-J 2 folders, 43-4 to 43-5
      - "(The)" Job of a Service Secretary, DPS Serial No. 103, Comments, 43-4
      - Miscellany, 43-5
    - Correspondence-K, 43-6
    - Correspondence-L, 43-7
    - Correspondence-M 3 folders, 43-8 to 43-10
      - Montgomery Visit, 43-8 to 43-9
      - Miscellany, 43-10
    - Correspondence-N 5 folders, 43-11 to 43-15
      - National War College, 43-11
      - Newsweek, 43-12
      - New York Times, 43-13
      - New York University, National Security Program, 43-14
      - Miscellany, 43-15
    - Correspondence-O 2 folders, 43-16 to 43-17
      - Ohio State University, 43-16
      - Miscellany, 43-17
    - Correspondence-P 3 folders, 43-18 to 43-20
      - Pictures-Admiral Gardner Session, DPS, December 16, 1954, 43-18
      - Pictures-Higgins Session, DPS, May 9, 1955, 43-19
      - Miscellany, 43-20
    - Correspondence-R 6 folders, 44-1 to 44-6
      - The Rand Corporation, 44-1
      - Ransom, Harry H. (Correspondence, Memos to and from), 44-2
      - Revue Militaire Generale, Paris, France-Correspondence, 44-3
      - Royal Institute of International Affairs (Chatham House)-Correspondence, 44-4
      - Royal United Service Institution Journal Article, 44-5
      - Miscellany, 44-6
    - Correspondence-S 7 folders, 44-7 to 44-13
      - Sallagar, Frederick M., 44-7
      - Slessor, Sir John, 44-8 to 44-11
      - Stanley, Timothy W., 44-12
      - Miscellany, 44-13
    - Correspondence-T, 44-14
    - Correspondence-U 8 folders, 45-1 to 45-8
      - University Relations-DPS-Bundy, 45-1
      - University Relations-Cavers, 45-2
      - University Relations-Committee Meetings Re DSP, 45-3
      - University Relations- Graduate School of Public Administration, 45-4 to 45-5
      - University Relations-President Nathan Pusey, 45-6
      - University Relations- Harvard Business School, 45-7
      - Miscellany, 45-8
    - Correspondence-V 2 folders, 45-9 to 45-10
      - vom Baur, F. Trowbridge, 45-9
      - Miscellany, 45-10
    - Correspondence-W, 45-11
    - Correspondence-Y, 45-12
    - Mailing Lists, 45-13
    - Miscellany 2 folders, 45-14 to 45-15
  - HARVARD MISCELLANY
    This Series consists of correspondence with colleagues, speeches at meetings of Harvard Clubs and Harvard Law School Associations throughout the country, and material relating to the Harvard Law Review, the Harvard Law School Model Trial, the Leach Club and other Harvard University activities. Period covered is 1930-1970.
    - Harvard Club of Boston 1967-1968, 46-1
    - Harvard Club of Eastern Maine, 46-2
      File relates to talk by WBL to Harvard Club of Eastern Maine, May 6, 1960.
    - Harvard Club of Washington, D.C. 1965, 46-3
    - Harvard College: Class of 1921, 46-4
      File relates to 45th Reunion of the Class.
    - Harvard College: Class of 1923, 46-5
    - Harvard Law Club of Alabama, 46-6
      File relates to talk given by WBL, March 6, 1959.
    - Harvard Law Review 1965-1968, 46-7
    - Harvard Law School: Ames Competition 1939-1947, 46-8
    - Harvard Law School:; Appointments Committee;; Planning Committee, 46-9
    - Harvard Law School Association of Delaware, 46-10
      File relates to talk given by WBL, April 12, 1967.
    - Harvard Law School Association of Indiana 1947, 46-11
    - Harvard Law School Association of Maine, 46-12
      File relates to talk given by WBL, May 20, 1959.
    - Harvard Law School Association of New Hampshire, 46-13
      File relates to speech given by WBL, May 17, 1961.
    - Harvard Law School Association of Southern California, 46-14
      File relates to talk given by WBL, November 12, 1959.
    - Harvard Law School Association of Western Pennsylvania 1966, 46-15
    - Harvard Law School:; Bok, Derek C. (Dean), 46-16
    - Harvard Law School Bulletin 1968-1969, 46-17
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1923, 46-18
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1924, 46-19
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1932, 46-20
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1934, 46-21
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1942, 46-22
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1943, 46-23
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1948, 46-24
    - Harvard Law School: Class of 1950, 46-25
    - Harvard Law School:; The Continuing Committee on Legal Education 1960-1969 2 folders, 46-26 to 46-27
    - Harvard Law School: Correspondence (chronological) 1958-1970 3 folders, 46-28 to 46-30
    - Harvard Law School: Endowment Fund 1967, 46-31
    - Harvard Law School: Faculty Letter Re Selective Service System 1966, 47-1
    - Harvard Law School: First Year Practice Exam 1966, 47-2
    - Harvard Law School: Information on Legal Practice in the Military 1966, 47-3
    - Harvard Law School:; Joint Student-Faculty Committee 1966-1967, 47-4
    - Harvard Law School:; Leach Club 1962-1966, 47-5
    - Harvard Law School: Lecture for Faculty Lecture Series, December 6, 1939, 47-6
    - Harvard Law School: Legal Education Career Conversation, March 19, 1967, 47-7
    - Harvard Law School Library 1967-1969, 47-8
    - Harvard Law School: Memoranda to the Faculty 1961-1970 2 folders, 47-9 to 47-10
    - Harvard Law School Model Trial, 1958, Marsh v. Fitch 4 folders, 47-11 to 47-14
      - Plaintiff, 47-11 to 47-12
      - Defendant, 47-13
      - Miscellaneous, 47-14
    - Harvard Law School:; Pow Wow Club, 47-15
      File relates to talk given by WBL, April 20, 1967.
    - Harvard Law School Record 1962-1969, 47-16
    - Harvard Law School:; Sacks, Albert H. (Dean), 47-17
    - Harvard Law School: Speech at Williston-Beale Dinner, May 19, 1938, 48-1
    - Harvard Law School: Speeches on Law to Entering and Prospective Students 1937-1969, 48-2
    - Harvard Law School: Speeches to Student Organizations 1930-1952, 48-3
    - Old Colony Harvard Club, 48-4
      File relates to speech by WBL, November 3, 1960.
    - Suggestions for Selection of Recipients of Honorary Degrees 1959-1960, 48-5
      File relates to letter sent by Professors Galbraith and Schlesinger to President Pusey protesting alleged discrimination against Democrats in the awarding of honorary degrees. WBL's humorous rebuttal is included in the file.
    - Miscellaneous Material, 48-6
  - BIOGRAPHICAL AND OTHER MISCELLANY